Ascending the West Tower of Fanlou
is not something I, Meng, can do.
I want to make a deal.
Please speak, Meng.
On the night of the Lantern Festival in three days,
you must leave three days' worth of medicine
for me.
How can we
trust you?
If you don't,
I will report to the authorities.
You are bandits,
and I know Dongjing like the back of my hand.
When you need to escape,
you can come find me again.
You have guts.
How do we ascend the tower?
I'm all ears.
Things I can't do,
I simply can't do.
You!
But I can take you to someone who can.
The place we're going,
only I, Meng Qian, can lead the way.
Are you talking about
Wuyou City?
Rumor has it that Wuyou City is full of
outlaws and eccentrics.
As long as you can afford the price,
any request will be fulfilled.
You've heard of it too, Taoist.
To tell you the truth,
I have indeed heard of it.
But this place is mysterious.
Ordinary people can't find it.
The Lantern Festival is approaching.
We have no choice but to come to you, Meng Qian.
We hope you can help us with all your might.
Since you all know it,
you should also know that
those who enter this city
will face near-certain death.
Have you all made up your minds?
Why the nonsense?
If we were to back down,
we wouldn't have come to Dongjing City.
This Wuyou City is indeed as rumors say.
Day and night are reversed,
and yin and yang are indistinguishable.
The compass is useless here.
Everyone, proceed with caution.
Have you been here?
I've only been this far.
Every step forward is new.
Pre-Qin ancient city.
I didn't expect
it to actually exist.
The direction of the miasma ahead is unclear.
We will wait for Brother Li Lang to return from scouting
before making any plans.
This Wuyou City has this miasma as a barrier.
No wonder the imperial soldiers have never set foot here.
My lord.
Did you see the situation inside the courtyard?
Not yet.
I only saw the person leading the horse enter the courtyard.
However,
the saddle on the horse is missing.
My lord.
I'll go in.
I am the best scout.
My Lord.
Xiao Wu, he...
Xiao Wu's Wall Gecko skill
is at 70% of his late brother's level.
Xiao Wu.
Commander Chu.
Search!
Good thing Brother Li Lang scouted ahead.
Otherwise, if we jumped into the miasma,
our flesh and skin
would have rotted into pus by now.
I risked my life just now
and barely managed to cross the miasma.
But you two brothers
and this brother probably can't.
I
actually have a way.
Everyone, be careful.
Man or ghost?
Man.
I am Zhu Zitong.
My respects to you all.
You came from the surface.
Have you seen
my daughter?
I have an only daughter,
who was abducted since childhood.
She was only
this big.
When her cruel mother came to find me,
she threw the baby daughter at me
and disappeared without a trace.
Later,
I watched her
grow up little by little.
She used to pull my beard,
and the white hairs that grew day by day,
to trade for malt sugar for me.
She had only eaten two of the ten pieces of malt sugar
when I watched helplessly as she was abducted.
Young man,
you know where my daughter is, right?
Tell me now!
Tell me!
This miasma is indeed powerful.
Daoist.
You know where my daughter is.
You can help me find her, right?
Brother,
seeing your extraordinary skills just now,
I haven't asked you
how I should address you.
I am but a humble man.
I hold a bright lantern
here to guide those
who intend to enter Wuyou City.
I lead the way.
Just call me
the Lantern Bearer.
The Lantern Bearer.
Old man,
since you can freely pass through this fog,
why not enter the city to find her yourself?
Of course I have.
But the Master of Wuyou Cave
won't accept my business.
I can only guide those entering and leaving Wuyou City,
praying that someone
can help me find my daughter.
But those who promised to help
never kept their word.
I hate them!
I hate them so much!
The Lantern Bearer can enter Wuyou City,
which already shows great skill.
It seems this Master of Wuyou Cave is not simple.
Everyone,
are you willing to help me find my daughter?
Brother,
I am truly sorry.
We have urgent matters to attend to,
so I'm afraid we can't help you.
Without me,
how will you pass through this miasma?
I have my own ways,
so don't you worry about it.
Although this miasma is poisonous,
fortunately,
I brought miasma-repelling pills.
Take this,
keep it under your tongue.
Do not swallow it.
My daughter!
How can I find you?
Old man.
Once I enter the city,
if there is a chance,
I will definitely ask about your daughter's whereabouts.
Young man,
why are you helping me?
I'll kill you!
My lord!
I will kill you!
Officer,
have mercy!
My lord,
focus on the big picture!
what are you saying?
Xiaowu,
I really don't know who he is.
I couldn't possibly have killed him.
Tell the truth.
I am
Liu Heizi,
from Dongjing.
What is your relationship with them?
What relationship could I have with them?
I'm just a lowly idler.
I happened to take a job
to deliver some goods here.
What are they doing here?
Do you know?
I...
I don't know.
They
are all mutes.
I am telling the truth.
If you don't believe me, you can send someone to check.
Got it.
If you dare to lie,
I'll stab you.
My Lord.
After him!
Yes.
Stop running! Stop!
Take him down!
Don't run!
Wait.
Under this well is Wuyou City,
which connects to the underworld.
If you have the guts,
then follow me.
Lord Duzhi.
There are too many forks down this well.
If we go too deep,
I'm afraid we won't catch Liu Heizi,
and we might trap ourselves instead.
A human's nose is never as sensitive as a dog's.
You are right, Lord Duzhi.